Previously on
Space Brothers
むった
＜不運に縁がある兄･六太と➡
Older brother Mutta is plagued by bad luck.
ひびと
栄光の日生まれの弟･日々人＞
Born under a lucky star, younger brother Hibito becomes the first Japanese moonwalker.
＜日本人初のムーン･ウォーカーと
なった日々人は 月面での➡
A lunar accident has left Hibito struggling on the sidelines, suffering from a panic disorder.
事故の影響でパニック障害となり
前線から外された＞
But he's able to pass a test to return to active duty.
＜しかし 復帰をかけた試験を➡
日々人は
何とか乗り越える事ができた＞
Older brother Mutta continues his long quest to the moon,
＜一方 日々人の遥か後ろから
月を目指し始めた兄･六太は➡
having finally been selected as a
backup member for a lunar mission.
ついに 月のミッションの
バックアップクルｰに任命された＞
＜そして今まさに 月を目指す
訓練が始まろうとしている！＞
And he's about to begin training for the moon.
よう ヒビト｡聞こえるか？
Hey, Hibito... Can you hear me?
Huh? Yeah...
なんば
(南波日々人)え？ああ…｡
《あれ…誰だ？》
Wait, who is that?
頼むぜ ヒビト｡
一緒にカイコ食った仲だろ？
Come on, Hibito...
We ate silkworms together.
あ…バディ！
Buddy!
こっからは俺が キャプコムを
やらせてもらうぜ｡へっへっへ…｡
I'll be taking over as CAPCOM.
おっと その前に｡上方からの
ゴンドラに気をつけろ｡
First, watch out for the gondola above you.
何で？
Why?
何でってことはないだろ｡
船外活動は基本的に➡
You have to ask why?
EVAs are supposed to be done with a partner.
パートナーと２人でやるもんだ｡
(ﾛｰﾘｰ)おめでとう ヒビト！
(ﾊﾞﾃﾞｨ)よくやった！
Congratulations, Hibito!
Great job!
I can't get lost in what I'm doing, nothing works out
I don't want these endlessly dull days
I hope I can move on
before the call of freedom drags me away
What's your wish?
I just want some real courage
We all stare doubt in the face, every one of us
Isn't the unpredictability of life the fun of it?
Devote your life to that dream you can't express
Let's go, advance against the wind, our road is long
Embrace the pain of it too
Take a big breath now, and yell
Big Bang! Chase it without fear!
I want to dream so badly it amazes me
There's cowardice in the way of your true wish
Rip that hot veil aside
#92 Lonely People
(ﾛｰﾘｰ)ヒヤッとする場面も
あったけどね なんのその！
There were a few close calls, but he aced the test!
ヒビトは やっぱり
サムライボーイだったよ！
Hibito's a true samurai boy.
見せたかったなぁ～｡
I wish you could have seen him...
Yeah, I expected as much.
まあ そ～だろうな｡
ちなみに俺は
そのサムライの兄だけどな｡
And don't forget that I'm the samurai boy's big brother.
帰ってからヒビトに ちゃんと
お祝いのハグしたかい？
Once you got home, did you give Hibito a celebratory hug?
ハグ ハグ～！
A big hug!
あのな ローリー｡日本の兄弟は➡
Now look here, Lowry...
In Japan, brothers don't hug.
“幼少期に生き別れ
２０年ぶりに奇跡の再開！"➡
Unless we're talking about a miraculous reunion,
…くらいのレベルでない限り
抱き合ったりしね～の｡
after being separated as children twenty years earlier.
残念だなぁ｡他のみんなは
ヒビトをハグしたってのに｡
That's too bad...
Everyone else gave Hibito hugs.
他のみんなって？
カレンやオリビアも？
Everyone else?
Including Karen and Olivia?
当然！
《マジかよ～》
Of course.
Seriously?
《なんだよ 日々人の野郎…》
Hibito, you lucky bastard.
I wanna take a test like him...
《俺も…復帰試験 受けてぇ…》
ところで ムッタはバックアップの
メンバｰに会うのは今日が初めて？
By the way, will this be your first time meeting the rest of the backup crew?
え…？あ ああ…｡
Huh?
Y-Yeah.
(ﾛｰﾘｰ)絶対じゃないんだけどさ…｡
It isn't set in stone...
セス
(職員)ＣＥＳ-６２の関係者は
こちらへ｡
Everyone involved with CES-62 should come this way.
それじゃ 僕のクルーは
あっちだから｡
おう｡
Well, my crew's meeting over there.
ウチュンチュ！
Space Man!
Sorry, Lowry...
《悪いな ローリー》
《やっぱりそれ どう見ても
うちゅうじん
宇宙人だわ》
In Japanese, that really just means "alien".
おっ…アンディ！
Andy!
(ｱﾝﾃﾞｨ)おう｡
Hey.
わ… おっと…｡
Oops...
アンディもＣＥＳ-６２の
バックアップ？
(ｱﾝﾃﾞｨ)そうだ｡
You're also on the CES-62 backup crew?
Yes.
じゃあ 俺と一緒だ！ヨロシク！
So am I! I can't wait to work together!
他にも この中に
あと何人かいるんだな｡
I guess the other crew members are already here.
宇宙飛行士のメンバーが｡
お前の横に １人いるよ｡
One of them is right next to you.
Huh?
(ﾌｨﾘｯﾌﾟ)♪～ブリブリ ブリブリ
ん ブリ？
よくこれがヘッドフォンだって
わかったね！
You knew these were headphones?
あっ 君
ヒビトのブラザーじゃん！
Wait! You're Hibito's brother!
Yah, man! Yah, man!
ヤァマン！ヤァマン！ヤァマン！
Yah, man!
ヤーマン…｡
Yah, man...
おやじ
親父はジャマイカ人
母ちゃんはアメリカ人で➡
My father was Jamaican, my mother American, and I was born in Argentina.
アルゼンチン生まれ
フィリップ･ルイスだ｡
The name's Philippe Louis.
I grew up in Argentina and Brazil, and now I'm enjoying life in Houston, USA.
アルゼンチンとブラジル育ちで➡
今はアメリカ
ヒューストンライフよ｡
I see...
なるほど 陽気なわけだ｡
ヤァマン！
That explains your sunny disposition.
Yah, man!
よ～し みんな集まったな｡➡
Okay, everyone's here?
Welcome to the Desert RATS training for CES-62.
ＣＥＳ-６２の
デザｰトラッツ訓練へ ようこそ｡➡
しけたツラが揃ったもんだ｡
I see some gloomy faces.
(ｼﾞｮｰｼﾞ)このグループの
訓練教官を任された➡
I've been named this group's training instructor.
I'm a geologist, George McGuire.
地質学者の
ジョージ･マグワイアだ｡
Giant and dreads!
そこのデカブツとドレッド頭！
お前ら 宇宙飛行士だな｡
You're astronauts, right?
そうです｡
ヤァマン！
Yes.
Yah, man!
やっぱりな｡
私は地質や石だけでなく➡
I thought so.
I am able to accurately analyze both rocks and people.
人を見抜く力もある｡
２人！前へ出ろ｡
Both of you, step forward.
それから…➡
Next...
そこの いけすかねぇ帽子のお前！
宇宙飛行士だろ｡
You there, with the ugly hat!
You must be an astronaut.
Looks like you're talking about me...
フフ…ご名答｡
Bingo.
やっぱりな｡
お前も前に出ろ｡
I knew it.
Step forward.
はいはい 逆らいませんよ
その定めには｡
Yes, yes...
I must obey my destiny.
やっぱり出ちゃうんだねぇ
宇宙飛行士のオーラが｡
I guess I just have the aura of an astronaut.
次は どいつだ…｡
And who's next?
(ベティ)私です｡悪いけど…➡
I am.
Sorry, but I didn't feel like waiting for you to find me.
面倒なのよね 待ってるの｡
なるほど お前か｡
まあ出てこなければ当てていた｡➡
You?
If you hadn't stepped forward, I would have identified you.
あと１人いるはずだ｡
There should be one more.
やあ｡
Hey.
バックアップの宇宙飛行士が…｡
One more backup astronaut...
さぁて どいつだ｡
Who is it?
《ここにいるよ～！ここ ここ！》
I'm right here... Right here!
《ほら！ここ気付いて！》
Come on, look at me.
《ちょっと！こっち見ろ～！》
Hey! Over here!
《おいっ！》
Hey!
お前か｡
Is it you?
いえ 違います｡
No, it isn't.
《…誰だよ それっ》
Hey, who is that?!
じゃあ お前か｡
いいえ｡
Is it you, then?
No.
お前だな？
違います｡
It must be you.
It isn't.
じゃあ お前｡
What about you?
No.
お前だろ｡
いいえ｡
Then, you.
Nope.
You.
お前だ｡
(男)いいえ｡
No.
やっぱりな そっちのお前だな｡
(男)違います｡
Thought so.
So it must be you.
It's not.
お前…か…？
Could it be you?
はい そ～ですけど…｡
Yes, it is...
やっぱりな 当たりだ｡
お前も前に出ろ｡
As always, I was right.
Now step forward.
《…当たりか？今の》
That counts as being right?
さぁて これで５人揃ったな｡
Okay, we have our five astronauts.
残念ながら 俺にも
君のは見えなかったよ｡
I'm sorry to say that I couldn't see the aura of an astronaut coming from you.
宇宙飛行士のオーラ｡
ヤァマン！
Huh?
Yah, man!
諸君！よく覚えておくんだ｡
Ladies and gentleman, pay close attention.
今 前に出た この５人が
君らが面倒を見ることになる➡
The five astronauts standing before you
will be your responsibility.
ＣＥＳ-６２の
バックアップクルーだ｡
They are the CES-62 backup crew.
⦅絶対じゃないんだけどさ➡
It isn't set in stone...
今日から一緒に訓練する
ﾊﾞｯｸｱｯﾌﾟｸﾙｰのﾒﾝﾊﾞｰってのはね➡
But the backup crew members you train with
そのまま一緒に 宇宙に行く
メンバーだと思っていいよ⦆
are very likely to be the crew members with whom you'll go into space.
《いつか このメンバーで
一緒に月へ…！》
These are the people I'll be going to the moon with.
And...
《しかも
あんな美人がいるなんて➡
There's a beautiful lady!
なんという幸運！》
I feel so lucky!
さぁて 他のグループは
ここで説明をやるようだが➡
Okay, other groups would hold an orientation session now,
ウチは実践主義だ｡
but I believe in practical training.
Let's head out!
(ｼﾞｮｰｼﾞ)出発するぞ！
North Arizona Black Point Lava Flow Training Grounds
(ｼﾞｮｰｼﾞ)荒れた地表 クレーター➡
Barren earth, craters,
険しい丘に急斜面➡
treacherous cliffs, steep slopes,
昼と夜の極端な温度差➡
extreme temperature swings between day and night,
かわどこ
干上がった河床
歩けば舞う砂ボコリ…｡
dried-up riverbeds, and clouds of dust with every step.
Well? Are you excited now?
どうだ ワクワクするだろう｡
It's as good as a theme park.
テーマパークなんかと
いい勝負だ｡
《まあ…間違いなく➡
Well...
I'm pretty sure a theme park would be more fun.
テーマパークの方が
楽しいだろうけど…》
《でも 俺も…
こんな砂漠でワクワクする➡
But I'm one of the weirdos who can get excited about barren desert.
変人の１人になってしまった》
見ろ お前らより
３日早く訓練を開始してる➡
Look.
It's the prime crew of CES-62.
ＣＥＳ-６２ 正規クルーの
お出ましだ｡
They started training three days ago.
おぉ～ ビンスさん！
わ～お みんな貫禄あるぅ～！
Hey, Vince!
Wow, they all look important...
(ｱﾝｶﾞｽ)オ～ウィ！
バックアップのみんな！
Hey, backup crew members!
Let's train hard!
お互い がんばってこ～ぜ！
は～い！
ヤァマン！
Yes!
Yah, man!
よっしゃ！
俺もドレッド全開でいこっ！
Okay, time to unleash my dreads!
《あれ…正規クルーは６人》
Huh? The prime crew has six members?
《こっちは１人足りねぇよな》
Then we're one short.
Is that supposed to happen?
《そ～いうこともあんのかな…》
ふ～っ あっついわね
ホントに１２月？
It's so hot...
And it's supposed to be December?
《この暑さに…感謝！》
I must thank the heat!
《いや それにしても
たくましいな この人》
Yeah, this woman is built...
《ん!?》
A heart tattoo... On her left shoulder!
《ハートマーク！しかも左肩!!》
Just like Apo!
《アポと同じ!!》
⦅奇遇だね⦆
⦅え？⦆
Funny thing...
Eh?
⦅ウチの愛犬にもあるんだ⦆
My pet dog also has a heart-shaped mark on his left shoulder.
⦅左肩に…ハートマークが⦆
⦅えっ そうなの!?⦆
Oh? Really?
⦅私たち 気が合いそうね⦆
I think we'll get along great.
⦅そのようだね⦆
Indeed.
⦅ウフフフ…⦆
⦅アハハハ…⦆
《…てな具合に➡
Yes, that is definitely
not what would happen!
いくわけね～だろ！》
《｢犬と同じ｣って言われて➡
Who wants to be compared to a dog?
誰が喜ぶんだ！
あぶね～ あぶね～》
I almost screwed up.
フッフフ…｡
何こっち見てんのよ
ブッ飛ばされたいの？
What are you looking at?
Want me to sock you?
フン！
いや…ソ ソーリー…｡
N-No, s-sorry...
Sh-She's strong.
《つ 強い！この人 強い！
そして 怖い》
She's really strong!
And scary.
バカだね～ 君は｡
You're such a fool...
ダメだよ｡ベティのこと
２秒以上見つめちゃ｡
You can't stare at Betty for longer than two seconds.
あんな美女が
男ばかりのクルーに➡
Why do you think they would assign a beautiful woman like her to a crew full of men?
女１人で入れる理由を
考えてごらんよ｡
It's because she's manlier than the rest of us.
(カルロ)つまりは
男より男らしいのさ｡
《なんと…》
Whoa.
来ました来ました≫
Okay, here we are!
(タリー)≪安全運転ありがとね≫
Thanks for driving safely.
But it turns out that any idiot can drive this thing safely.
≪と言ってもバカでも
安全運転できるんだ コイツは≫
This would place last in a Formula 1.
(タリー)≪Ｆ－１レースじゃ
最下位だろうけど➡
But it rules on the moon.
月面じゃ最強のマシンなのだよ｡
ヘヘン≫
(タリー)どもどもみなさん
僕 タリーです｡
Hello, everyone...
I'm Tully.
よろしく どもども｡
え～っと 僕は君たちに➡
Nice to meet you all.
So, I'm supposed to teach you how to operate this thing.
コイツの操作を
教えなきゃならない｡➡
といっても もう知ってる人も
いると思うけど 知ってるかな？➡
But I imagine that some of you already know how it works, right?
Am I right?
エスイーブイ
知ってるよね？ご存知｢ＳＥＶ｣
通称ビートルだ｡ヘヘン｡
As you know, this is the SEV, also known as the Beetle.
コイツの開発費は７０億ドル｡
It cost seven billion dollars to develop!
On my salary, I couldn't afford that in a thousand lifetimes.
僕の年収だと
人生千回やってもまだ足りないね｡
いや 来世でハリウッドスターに
なってればいけるかもな｡
Well, if I become a Hollywood star in my next life, I might have a chance...
やった 希望が見えてきた｡
Yes! I have hope!
タリー 余計な話は省け｡
Tully, stop getting sidetracked.
あ そうだね｡
ごめんよジョージ｡ヘヘン｡
Oh, of course...
Sorry, George.
チッ ジョージのおサル野郎め｡
あんたが余計なんだよ｡➡
Damn that ape.
You're the distraction here.
Keep your mouth shut!
静かにしてろ｡そんなんだから
奥さんが逃げて行くんだよ｡➡
That's why your wife left you.
Not that I have a wife.
まあ 僕もいないけど｡
俺は生まれ変わっても
また俺になりたいね｡
In my next life, I hope to be myself again.
タイヤは水平方向に360度ぐるっと
向きを変えられる｡➡
The tires can turn 360 degrees, so it can move sideways, like a crab.
だから カニみたいに
横移動も可能なんだ｡➡
There are living quarters inside, so it's like a lunar RV.
中は居住スペースにもなってるし
言ってみれば月面ｷｬﾝﾋﾟﾝｸﾞｶｰだね｡➡
Does everyone like to camp?
みんなキャンプとか好きでしょ？
僕は嫌い｡➡
I hate it.
後ろに宇宙服がくっついてるのは
知ってるよね｡➡
You already know that the spacesuits attach to the back, right?
Right now, they're inside the glove.
今はこのグラブの中｡➡
ああ グラブって
このカバーのことね｡➡
Oh, the glove is this cover.
何かの幼虫っぽいよね｡宇宙服を
レゴリスなんかから守るものだ｡
Reminds you of larva, yes?
Its purpose is to protect spacesuits from regolith.
こんな便利なものがあるのに
宇宙飛行士たちは面倒臭がって➡
It's a convenient tool, but astronauts hate using it...
使おうとしないんだ｡まったく…
みんなのために必死になって➡
Honestly, do they realize how hard we're working on their behalf?
考えた こっちの身にも
なってほしいよ｡
何か質問ある人なんている？
Does anyone have any questions?
ないよね｡あっそう｡
Nope... Of course.
フゥーッ！
Okay, raise the glove.
(ｼﾞｮｰｼﾞ)よ～し
グラブを上げろ｡
きた～！
There they are!
《月面用の宇宙服！➡
Spacesuits for walking on the moon!
うお～ 今からこれ着れんのかぁ！
とうとうきた～！》
I'm about to put one on?
It's finally time!
まずはこの宇宙服を着る訓練だ｡
誰からいく？
You'll start by learning to put the spacesuit on.
Who wants to go first?
んじゃまあ 俺が｡
Then, I'll go first.
Hold on...
ちょっと待ちなよ｡
お!?なんだよ！
Huh? What is it?
君はそんなだから
そんななんだよ｡ベティ！
And that is exactly your problem.
Betty...
さあ 君こそ最初にふさわしい｡
どうも カルロ｡
You should have the honor of going first.
I appreciate it, Carlo.
だけど ワザとらしい
レディファーストは➡
But you're still a chauvinist pig.
気持ち悪いだけよ｡
ホント 気持ち悪ぃ！
Yeah, oink oink.
君に先に使われたくないだけだよ｡
I didn't want you to wear the spacesuit first.
After all, you probably don't wash those dreads.
だって 洗ってないんだろ？
そのドレッド｡
(ﾌｨﾘｯﾌﾟ)あ 洗ってるよ！
５日に１回くらいは！
(カルロ)５日？
I wash them! Once every five days!
Five days?
《うるさい連中ね》
These guys are so noisy...
アンディもモアイみたいに
黙ってないで➡
Don't just stand there like a moai...
このキザ野郎に何か
言ってやれ！ホレ！
Tell that sleazeball off, man.
毎日洗った方がいい｡
You should wash them every day.
お前が行け｡
You go first.
あ ああ はい｡
O-Okay.
《な なんだろう このチーム…》
What's up with this team?
Take a sniff... They don't smell!
ニオイかいでみろよ！
臭くないから！
イヤだ｡
見苦しい｡
No way.
Pathetic.
(ｼﾞｮｰｼﾞ)騒ぐな！
宇宙服はまだ２つある｡
Keep it down! There are two more spacesuits!
《全然…一緒に宇宙へ
行ける気がしない》
I can't see myself going to space with them.
(ﾊﾞﾄﾗｰ)ＣＥＳ-６２の正規クルーは
いいメンツです｡➡
The CES-62 prime crew features a strong lineup...
Angus, Bold, Larry, and Tara.
アンガスにボールド君
ラリー君 ターラもいる｡➡
何の心配もない｡
ただ 問題なのは➡
They should do just fine.
However, the sub crew concerns me.
サブクルーのメンツです｡
(役員)と いいますと？
What do you mean?
ひとくせ
ふたくせ
あれは 一癖も二癖もある
連中の寄せ集めです｡
The sub crew is comprised of some unique characters.
アンディ･タイラーは
無口さとあの巨体が醸し出す➡
With his silence and giant size, Andy Tyler can scare people off.
異様な雰囲気のせいで怖がられ➡
ベティ･レインは
強い態度と物言いが➡
Betty Rain's aggressive tone and behavior makes it seem as though she's keeping people away.
まるでバリアでも張っているかの
ようで近寄りがたい｡➡
カルロ･グレコは気取った言動に
嫌気が差した周囲から➡
Carlo Greco is disliked because of his haughty demeanor.
疎ましがられ
フｨリｯプ･ルイスはムダに陽気で➡
Philippe Louis is usually too loud and happy for everyone else.
騒がしい あのノリに
誰もついていけない｡
なるほど…困ったもんですな｡
I understand... This could be a problem.
残念ながら 本心から彼らと共に
宇宙へ行きたがる者はいません｡
Unfortunately, no one wants to go to space with them.
考え抜いた結果が➡
That's why we ended up putting them together.
なか
半ばやけっぱちの
この組み合わせです｡
どうしようもない孤独な彼らを
一緒のチームにさせ➡
We assigned the lonely astronauts to the same team,
そこに ナンバ･ムッタという男を
放り込む｡➡
and then we added Nanba Mutta.
それがどう作用するのか
しないのか➡
Whether this works or not will be a gamble.
ある意味 ギャンブルです｡
そして あともう１人➡
And with one more person,
このクルーのキｬプテンが決まれば
なんとかなるかもしれません｡
the captain of the crew,
it just might work.
あては あるんですか？
Do you know who you'll turn to?
Yes.
(ﾊﾞﾄﾗｰ)メールでは
一度断られましたが…➡
When I sent an e-mail, I was turned down...
But I have a candidate.
一人…｡
The starlight illuminates my future, it's wow... truth
It's 3 AM, and I dream awake
With no idea of my future
only impatience consumes me
I have a thorn in my heart that won't allow me to lose to him
I'm walking a path of thorns I made for myself
But I won't forget the love I found
And I won't forget the ones close to me
I realized you cannot live your life alone
The starlight illuminates my future, and we are all shooting stars
My holy wishes turn all our sad lies into something better
Our orbits have gotten separated,
but I'm fine if you are close
Next time, on
Space Brothers
#93 In the Corner of My Heart
If he agrees to be captain of Nanba Mutta's team, it just might work.
(ﾊﾞﾄﾗｰ)＜南波六太たちのチームは
あの男が キャプテンを➡
引き受けてくれれば
なんとかなるかもしれません＞
Meanwhile, Sharon has come to Houston.
＜一方 その頃 シャロンが
ヒューストンへ やってくる＞
Next time, on Space Brothers:
"In the Corner of My Heart"
Mr. Hibbit!
一体何が起こってるんだ!?
What's going on?
第５ﾓｼﾞｭｰﾙで火災発生！
消火ｼｽﾃﾑ故障｡爆発の恐れあり｡
Fire detected in Module 5.
Fire-suppression system is malfunctioning.
Possibility of explosion.
(ﾊﾞﾃﾞｨｺﾞﾘﾗ)うわわ！すぐに
脱出しないとマズイぞ！
Don't we need to get out of here?
でも 脱出用のビートルは
充電が終わるまで動けないわ！
But we can't leave until Beetle finishes charging.
逃げ場がないってことか｡
So we have nowhere to run?
にゃんとかにゃらないの!?
Isn't there anything we can do?
Let's find a way!
(ﾋﾋﾞｯﾄ)≪なんとかしようよ！≫
(ﾋﾋﾞｯﾄ)みんな！それぞれの力を
出し合おう｡
Everyone, it's time to combine our powers!
Use whatever you've got.
みんなの持ってるもの｡
(ﾌﾚﾃﾞｨﾄﾞｯｸﾞ)ワン｡
Freddy Dog can provide experience and leadership.
(ﾋﾋﾞｯﾄ)ﾌﾚﾃﾞｨﾄﾞｯｸﾞは
経験と統率力を｡➡
ﾀﾞﾐｱﾝﾎｰｸは技術を｡➡
Damian Hawk provides technical expertise.
ﾊﾞﾃﾞｨｺﾞﾘﾗは その腕力を｡➡
Buddy Gorilla provides brawn.
ﾚｯｻｰﾘﾝﾀﾞとｶﾚﾝｷｬｯﾄは
知識と保護を｡
Red Panda Linda and Karen Cat provide knowledge and support.
今こそ みんなの力が必要だ｡
この場を頼む｡
It's time to unite...
I'll let you guys handle this!
Wait up, Hibbit...
(ﾊﾞﾃﾞｨｺﾞﾘﾗ)ちょっと待て ヒビット！
Are you going to Module 5 alone?
１人で第５ﾓｼﾞｭｰﾙへ行く気か！
危険すぎる！
It's too dangerous.
Someone has to go and stop the place from exploding!
誰かが行って爆発を止めないと！
だが…｡
行かせてくれ！
But...
Let me do this!
僕が持ってるのは…
勇気と元気だけなんだ！
All I can provide is courage and energy!
Yay!
イェーイ！
H-Hibbit!
(ﾊﾞﾃﾞｨｺﾞﾘﾗ)ヒ ヒビット！
(ﾀﾞﾐｱﾝﾎｰｸ)行くなぁ ヒビット！
Don't go, Hibbit!
See you next week!